# SAHIL BHARDWAJ

Full-stack Developer

Sahil Bhardwai ambaysb@gmail.com

+91-9017800099 github.com/evoxf1

New Delhi, India in linkedin.com/in/evoxf1l

### **SUMMARY**

A mechanical engineer by eductaion and fun-loving Fullstack developer by luck. Expertise in web technologies and algorithms, optimizing softwares and creating beautiful websites. Committed to continuous learning and dedicated to creating lasting digital footprints through precision and innovation.

**SKILLS** 

Forte JavaScript, HTML, CSS, TypeScript Languages:

Familiar GO, Python

Technologies: ReactJS, MongoDB, ExpressJS, NextJS,

Tailwind.

### **PROJECTS**

Next IS-TS **Portfolio** LIVE

> A captivating project, meticulously crafted with leading frameworks and libraries demonstrating the skills of myself. Implemented email functionality using React-Email. Used Framer-motion for animations and

MERN-TS Social-Networking App

LIVE A social networking app with login functionality with Oauth, adding friends and commenting on their posts

and much more.

Scribble Sketch App NextJS-Socket.io

A scribble app that runs using websockets and can be used by multiple people at the same time. So go

and play a tic-tac-toe match.

MERN-TS LIVE **Shopping App** 

A faithful recreation with registration, login, and integrated Stripe and PayPal payments for a true online shopping experience.

# **EXPERIENCE**

4/2022 - Present Full-stack Developer

Private

LIVE

- Continuously improving web development skills through self-study and online courses.
- Currently learning HTML, CSS, JS, TS, Python and MERN Stack to build dynamic and interactive web applications.

# 

Shri Ganpati Enterprises

- Started working for the company as a Solar Energy expert but helped it to enter the web development
- Provided services relating to IT and Web Development and making small HTML Templates from Figma Stylesheets along with Solar Energy conservation benefits and tips to clients

# 4/2018 - 3/2019 **Marketing Executive**

Ecoleaf Energies Pvt. Ltd.

- · Created Clients for roof top solar power plants.
- · Industrial Goods trading for clients in and outside India
- · Handled IT related tasks for the company

#### 7/2016 - 4/2018 **Junior Engineer Trainee**

Modern Prefab Systems Pvt. Ltd

 Building fabricated shelters, Steel frames, manufacturing and erection of single, double and triple story Pre-Fabricated shelters.

## **EDUCATION**

2016 PDM College Of Engineering, Bahadurgarh **Bachelor** 

Completed a full-time Mechancial Engineering Degree

**CBSE** 2012 School

Graduated High School with PCM

## **LANGUAGES**